[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 40,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9901_0036_d_00_container_masterofthetempest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9919_MSQ_WardenScout",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_36",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_35 || 99D_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Into the Depths",
        "Description": "Chase after the retreating Commander Thorpe. Make your way through the Depths and take him down.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Were you able to track Thorpe?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "It was almost too easy. He took his frustration out on every village he passed by.\\n\\nAll I had to do was follow the trail of destruction, which lead to here.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If you do find Thorpe… make him suffer.\\n\\nIf I live six more centuries, I'll never forget what he did.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You… you survived…? And your eyes, you're not even Corrupted.\\n\\nDid you find him? Did you actually defeat Thorpe?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9910_0056_thetempestsheart",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9910_0056_d_00_container_thetempestsheart",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0717_Warden",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_56",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_55",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9910_0056_thetempestsheart_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Fortress at the Threshold",
        "Description": "Find the Soulwardens at Mountainhome Outpost, and offer your help.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"That's when the Tempest's soul touched shore.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Is that right? I bet the Corruption sensed it. \\n\\nHuman souls tend to be pretty noisy.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If you so happen back this way, feel free to bring some fish.\\n\\nSlim pickings around here.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well, I was wondering if you'd ever join us here on the front lines. Though you might be too late. \\n\\nIf you haven't heard yet, we may be on the verge of abandoning this position.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0057_insoulinstone",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9901_0057_d_00_container_insoulinstone",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0717_Warden",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_57",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_56 || 99E_MSQ_11",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0057_insoulinstone_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "QuestReward_MSQFinale",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Heart of the Tempest",
        "Description": "Enter the Tempest's Heart Expedition and look for the Tempest herself -  Captain Isabella - and then confront her and put an end to her campaign of Corruption.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'm actually going in.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I'm sorry… I think I misheard you. Did you say you need to check in at the inn? \\n\\nPerfectly understandable. I know you've been on a long journey. It's right over there, of course.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I'll say this much, you've got sand.\\n\\nGo on then - kick the Tempest's ass. The Soulwardens, those of us who remain,  we're behind you all the way.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Wow, you look like hell. It must've been a fight for the ages. We saw the change in the Mountain.\\n\\nDoes that mean… I can't believe I'm saying this - is the Tempest destroyed?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": true,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9910_0058_finallyexhale",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9910_0058_d_00_container_finallyexhale",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9905e_MSQ_Rima",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_58",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_57",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9910_0058_finallyexhale_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Finally, Exhale",
        "Description": "Tell your friends the good news.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I can't argue with that.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I'm sure there are other people all over Aeternum who would welcome this news.\\n\\nI'll leave it to you to share the good word. Thank you, {playerName}. I never thought this day would come.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I think it's going to take some time for me to really internalize this turn of events.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "If we don't have hope, what do we have?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": true,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9905_0059_InMemoriam",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9910_0059_d_00_container_InMemoriam",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9928_MSQ_YonasMemorial",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_59",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_58",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9905_0059_InMemoriam_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "In Memoriam",
        "Description": "Gather tokens of remembrance from your companions, and set them at a memorial to Yonas at Fisherman's Bend.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "If we don't have hope, what do we have?",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I've heard that some of the Soulwardens have built a memorial to Yonas at his old place by the river.\\n\\nHere's a token of my own favor, do you think you could go to Emile and Theo and ask them for their own?\\n\\nI think it would be best if you represented us all, and brought those tokens home to him.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I don't know if we will ever be able to put Old Yonas to rest, but we can memorialize his sacrifice, and his valor.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "(The cold stone sits, quietly inert)",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": true,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9926_0101_TenaciousRose",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 20,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9926_0101_d_00_container_TenaciousRose",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9926_VK_AbigailRoseB",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "VarangianKnights_0101",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9926_0101_TenaciousRose_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Tenacious Rose",
        "Description": "Mysterious Raiders have taken over the ruins of Stonereach Keep where Abigail Rose was living. She's asked you to help figure who they are, why they're here and how she can get rid of them.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Whoa, easy! You seem a bit jumpy.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Out here, that's a critical trait, lest you wind up Corrupted or Lost! \\n\\nAnd don't try to tell me a settlement would be safer! I'll not be trusting my fate to some bumbling constable!",
        "InProgressResponse": "Have you figured out what these trespassers are doing in my Keep?\\n\\nWhatever it takes to get rid of them, I'm up for it.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Ah, you dealt that laughing bastard a thrashing? Well done! The wolves finally met a more vicious wolf! \\n\\nThis doesn’t mean I trust you, by the way. But I can’t argue with your results. Did you learn why they're here?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9926_0103_LostScarecrow",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 28,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9926_0103_d_00_container_LostScarecrow",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9930_VK_RomacBarboB",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "VarangianKnights_0103",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9926_0103_LostScarecrow_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Lost Scarecrow",
        "Description": "Locate Abigail Rose's missing companion, and find any evidence that points to what the Varangian Knights are searching for.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What are you doing here?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "My partner and I have been watching this camp for some time, and he moved closer to get a better look. Keep hoping for some sign from him, but nothing yet.\\nView is limited, and the patrols are thick.\\n\\nYou... wouldn't be interested in helping me again, would you?",
        "InProgressResponse": "Stick to the shadows, move slowly... and when the time is right, take them down. That's how we'll get these fools off our land.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Thanks for your help back there. I'm going to rest here for a bit, then take the long way back to the south. Don't want to have any other accidental run-ins with those armored cretins. Much better at staying out of sight than in a brawl. Abigail will be waiting for my report.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9932_0104_RelicReclamation",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 30,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9932_0104_d_00_container_RelicReclamation",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9931_VK_Caoimhe",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "VarangianKnights_0104",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9932_0104_RelicReclamation_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Relic Reclamation",
        "Description": "Find the notebook carried south by the Varangian Knights by speaking with the apprentice Caoimhe",
        "PlayerPrompt": "(Read the note)",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "To the one who finds this:\\nI have been taken by the Varangians, those cretins who seek to unlock the mysteries of Myrddin's experiments. Given my treatment at their hands, they won't use them for anything good.",
        "InProgressResponse": "You must head south. There is a woman there, Caoimhe, an apprentice to an Antiquarian. She is an ally, and familiar with the magics of the island.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Welcome back! Did you find the notebook for Romac?\\nWait, he wanted me to have it? If this holds the location to Myrddin's true workshop, this is a valuable - and dangerous - find. I... think I shall keep this from the Antiquarian. I know just where to hide it.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": true
    }
]
